<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pawfect</string>

    <string name="opendrawer">Open the Navigator</string>

    <string name="closedrawer">Close the Navigator</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="raj">lived in the bustling city of Tokyo, Japan. Every morning, Hachiko accompanied Professor Ueno, his owner to the Shibuya train station before he left for work. And like clockwork, every evening, Hachiko awaited his return. Their ritual became a symbol of their unspoken connection.

But fate played its part when Professor Ueno passed away unexpectedly. Day after day, year after year, Hachiko faithfully returned to the Shibuya train station, waiting patiently for his beloved owners return. It must have been a heart shattering sight to see.
Hachikos devotion spread like wildfire, touching everyones hearts. The loyal dogs presence at the station became a beacon of hope and a statement of loyalty for the country to honour and respect.
As you dive deeper into Hachikos tale, prepare to be moved by his unwavering loyalty and the impact he had on the lives of those around him. Join us as we pay tribute to the extraordinary life of Hachiko, a dog whose story continues to inspire generations with its timeless lessons of loyalty, devotion and love.</string>

    <string name="mega">In 1934, a statue of Hachiko was unveiled at a grand ceremony in front of Shibuya train station with Hachiko himself present as the main guest.
Also on the wall of the Shibuya Station, there is a huge beautiful mosaic artwork of Hachiko:
Hachiko passed away peacefully and alone on the street near Shibuya train station on March 8, 1935.
Hachiko is now on display at the National Science Museum in Ueno, Tokyo.
Today the Hachiko bronze statue is a popular attraction outside of Shibuya train station, especially among young Japanese. Also on the wall of the Shibuya Station, there is a huge beautiful mosaic artwork of Hachiko.
As a tribute to Hachiko multiple movies have been made in Japan to showcase the love and devotion of humans and their pets.</string>
</resources>